Preliminary Guide to the Pamela Jordan Yale School of Drama Scrapbook Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Pamela Jordan Yale School of Drama Scrapbook Collection
1966-2008
DRA 14
Yale University Arts Library
20
(35 boxes)
Collection of scrapbooks documenting the activities of the Yale School of Drama, Yale Repertory Theatre, and Yale Cabaret, 1966-2008.
Yale University. Drama Library
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Pamela Jordan Yale School of Drama Scrapbook Collection was housed in the former Drama Library until its transfer to the Robert B. Haas Family Arts Library in 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Pamela C. Jordan served the Yale School of Drama Library for 34 years. In that time she assisted numerous artists, faculty, staff, and students in their research and production work, and served as the documentarian for the Yale School of Drama and Yale Repertory Theatre activities.
Scope and Contents
Collection of scrapbooks documenting the activities of the Yale School of Drama, Yale Repertory Theatre, and Yale Cabaret, 1966-2008.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically.
Scrapbooks; Scrapbooks; Yale School of Drama
- Box listing
  Arrangement
  Key to Abbreviations: YSD = Yale School of Drama; YRT = Yale Repertory Theatre
  - YSD, 1966-1967; 13 x 15 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - YSD, 1966-1967 1967-1968; 17 x 18 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - YRT, 1967-1968; 12 x 16 x 2 inches (Box 1)
  - YSD/YRT, 1968-1969; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 2)
  - YRT, 1969-1970; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 2)
  - YRT, 1970; 15 x 14 x 2 inches (Box 2)
  - YSD, 1969-1970 1970-1971; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 3)
  - YRT, 1970-1971; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 3)
  - YRT, 1971-1972; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 4)
  - YSD, 1971-1972 1972-1973; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 4)
  - YRT, 1972-1973; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 5)
  - YSD, 1973-1974; 16 x 18 x 2 inches (Box 6)
  - YRT, 1973-1974; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 6)
  - YSD, 1974-1975; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 7)
  - YRT, 1974-1975; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 7)
  - YSD, 1975-1976; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 8)
  - YRT, 1975-1976; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 8)
  - YSD, 1976-1977; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 9)
  - YRT, 1976-1977; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 9)
  - YRT, 1977-1978; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 10)
  - YSD, 1977-1978; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 10)
  - YRT, 1978-1979; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 11)
  - YSD, 1978-1979; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 11)
  - YRT, 1979-1980; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 12)
  - YSD, 1979-1980; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 12)
  - YSD, 1980-1981; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 13)
  - YRT, 1980-1981; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 13)
  - YSD, 1981-1982; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 14)
  - YRT, 1981-1982; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 14)
  - YSD, 1982-1983; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 15)
  - YRT, 1982-1983; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 15)
  - YSD, 1983-1984; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 16)
  - YRT, 1983-1984; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 16)
  - YSD, 1984-1985; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 17)
  - YRT, 1984-1985; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 17)
  - YRT, Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1984-1985; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 18)
  - YRT, Fences, 1986; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 18)
  - YSD, 1985-1986; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 19)
  - YRT, 1985-1986; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 19)
  - YRT, 1986-1987 (Box 20)
  - YSD, 1986-1987; 2; 19 x 23 x 1 inches (Box 21)
  - Yale Cabaret, 1983-1985; 16 x 19 x 2 inches (Box 22)
  - Yale Cabaret, 1985-1987; 16 x 19 x 2 inches (Box 22)
  - Yale Cabaret, 1988-1992; 16 x 19 x 2 inches (Box 23)
  - YRT, 1987-1988; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 1 inches (Box 24)
  - August Wilson Plays, 1987-1988; 12.5 x 14.5 x 1 inches (Box 24)
  - YSD, 1987-1988; 3; 12.5 x 14.5 x 1 inches (Box 24)
  - YRT, 1988-1989; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 1 inches (Box 24)
  - YSD, 1988-1989; 4; 12.5 x 14.5 x 1 inches (Box 25)
  - August Wilson Plays, 1989-1990; 12 x 13 x 1 inches (Box 25)
  - YSD, 1989-1990; 4; 12 x 13 x 1 inches (Box 25)
  - YRT, 1989-1990; 2; 12 x 13 x 1 inches (Box 26)
  - YRT, 1990-1991; 2; 12 x 13 x 1 inches (Box 26)
  - YSD, 1990-1991; 3; 12 x 13 x 1 inches (Box 26)
  - YRT, 1991-1992; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 27)
  - YSD, 1991-1992; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 27)
  - YRT, 1992-1993; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 27)
  - YSD, 1992-1993; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 28)
  - YRT, 1993-1994; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 28)
  - YSD, 1993-1994; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 28)
  - YRT, 1994-1995; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 29)
  - YSD, 1994-1995; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 29)
  - YRT, 1995-1996; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 29)
  - YSD, 1995-1996; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 30)
  - YRT, 1996-1997; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 30)
  - YSD, 1996-1997; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 30)
  - YSD, 1997-1998; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 31)
  - YSD, 1998-1999; 2; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 31)
  - YRT, 1997-1998; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 32)
  - YRT, 1999-2000; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 32)
  - YSD, 1999-2000; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 32)
  - YRT, 2000-2001; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 32)
  - YSD, 2000-2001; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 33)
  - YRT, 2001-2002; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 33)
  - YSD, 2001-2002; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 33)
  - YRT, 2002-2003; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 33)
  - YSD, 2002-2003; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 34)
  - YRT, 2003-2004; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 34)
  - YSD, 2003-2004; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 34)
  - YSD/YRT, 2004-2005; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 35)
  - YSD/YRT, 2005-2006; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 35)
  - YSD/YRT, 2006-2007; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 35)
  - YSD/YRT, 2007-2008; 12.5 x 14.5 x 2 inches (Box 35)